Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben and Jerry's flavors, but
lower in calories and higher in protein.
This is the [music] Tonight. Let me show
you how to make it.
>> Almost 40 g protein.
We're starting off with a chocolate
base. So, I use one chocolate protein
shake. You can either use a prepackaged
one like the one I used or make your own
with a cup and a half of your favorite
milk and [music] a scoop of chocolate
protein powder. You're also going to
need some extra cocoa powder, sweetener,
salt, and zantham gum. Then you're going
to freeze your pint for at least 16
hours or until it's completely frozen
through. Run it under hot water for
about 30 to 60 seconds and then throw in
your creamy on the light ice cream set.
It'll probably come out a little bit
powdery like this. [music] But as you
can tell, the sides are slightly melted,
which means it is ready for the mixing
cycle. So, we're going to add in two
Oreo thins, cream removed, just to save
on a few calories. Run on the mixing
cycle. Then, we're going to top it with
our protein cookie dough. Always use the
one from Fuel. It's my favorite one.
Only one that tastes remotely like real
cookie dough. And of course, we're not
forgetting the caramel aspect of the
tonight dough.